Build A Little World with Me
Laura Shigihara
《建造一方小天地》
本视频含有剧透内容
如有在意请选择性观看
Once these walls were grey
四周灰白的孤壁
But you made stars and skys and snowflakes
因为有你熠熠生辉
We found a rainbow everywhere
世界染上了丰富的色彩
You made a place so we could hide away
你搭起了我们的乌托邦
And if you stay right by my side
如果你与我形影相随
We'll make it through the night
我们能一同渡过难关
And you'll never have to feel alone again
你也再不必茕茕孑立
So before it's time to leave
在那离别的前夕
Would you build a little world with me
你能否与我
建造一方小天地
Once this room was cold
病房孤寂阴冷
But then I asked the sun to smile again
我却依旧从中寻乐
Our castle cover the expanse
看到那城堡一望无际
With all the patches, pillows we could hold
我们抱着枕头玩具嬉戏
And if I stay right by your side
如果我和你不离不弃
We'll make it through the night
我们能一同渡过难关
And I'll never have to feel alone again
我也不会再感到孤寂
So before it's time to leave
在那离别的前夕
Would you build a little world with me
你能否与我
建造一方小天地
If you stay right by my side
如果你与我形影相随
We'll make it through the night
我们能一同渡过难关
And we'll never have to feel alone again
我们也不再形单影只
So before it's time to leave
在那离别的前夕
Would you build a little world with me
你能否与我
建造一方小天地
Now it's time for me to leave
分手之日悄然来临
I'm glad you built this little world
我很开心
你与我一同建造了
With me
一方天地
中英文翻译字幕 RigoLigo
软件 Aegisub 3.2.2
FFmpeg N-93005-gd92f06eb66
Adobe Premiere CC 2018
Adobe Media Encoder CC 2018
所有视频片段均来自作者计算机
使用Microsoft Game DVR功能录制
感谢观看